<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Projects on Joan Claverol - Data Analyst</title>
    <link>/projects/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Projects on Joan Claverol - Data Analyst</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="/projects/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Individual household electric power consumption</title>
      <link>/projects/submetter-smart-homes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/submetter-smart-homes/</guid>
      <description>OVERVIEW
Have you ever considered if it is worth it to install smart submeters at your place? And, in case you did it, how are you going to use them to help you with reducing the energy expenses and decrease the costs?
The main goal of this project is to detect which are the main advantages of submeters through data. I am going to focus on:
 Energy forecasting of the total house Appliance analysis Anomalies detection  Everything will be summarised in a dashboard where the final user will be able to track every aspect of the home.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wifi Indoor Positioning</title>
      <link>/projects/wifi-positioning/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/wifi-positioning/</guid>
      <description>OVERVIEW
Many real-world applications need to know the localization of a user in the world to provide their services. Therefore, automatic user localization has been a hot research topic in the last years. Automatic user localization consists of estimating the position of the user (latitude, longitude, and altitude) by using an electronic device, usually a mobile phone. Outdoor localization problem can be solved very accurately thanks to the inclusion of GPS sensors into the mobile devices.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Amazon reviews</title>
      <link>/projects/amazon-reviews/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/amazon-reviews/</guid>
      <description>OVERVIEW
Is it possible to predict the number of starts a user will give to a product based on the content of his review? Am I able to find different customer behaviours based on different products?
To be able to answer these questions will give me a better perspective of how customer client departments work on E-Commerce companies and do text mining to extract insights from it.

DATASET</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Avocado prices</title>
      <link>/projects/avocado-prices/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/avocado-prices/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Who eats the food we grow?</title>
      <link>/projects/world-food/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/world-food/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>