<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Joan Claverol - Data Analyst</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Joan Claverol - Data Analyst</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 03 Jun 2020 17:34:14 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Airbnb New York</title>
      <link>/blog/airbnb-newyork/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 May 2020 20:58:32 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/airbnb-newyork/</guid>
      <description>OVERVIEW
The main goal is to understand though visualizations how the prices for Airbnb in New York are distributed. To achieve that, we will use a kaggle dataset provided by Airbnb. First, we will look at the whole city, and then we will analyze each neighborhood.
The following map shows us the price distribution in the city of New York.
There is a big amount of options with high prices in the area of Manhattan.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Individual household electric power consumption</title>
      <link>/projects/submetter-smart-homes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/submetter-smart-homes/</guid>
      <description>OVERVIEW
Have you ever considered if it is worth it to install smart submeters at your place? And, in case you did it, how are you going to use them to help you with reducing the energy expenses and decrease the costs?
The main goal of this project is to detect which are the main advantages of submeters through data. I am going to focus on:
 Energy forecasting of the total house Appliance analysis Anomalies detection  Everything will be summarised in a dashboard where the final user will be able to track every aspect of the home.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wifi Indoor Positioning</title>
      <link>/projects/wifi-positioning/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/wifi-positioning/</guid>
      <description>OVERVIEW
Many real-world applications need to know the localization of a user in the world to provide their services. Therefore, automatic user localization has been a hot research topic in the last years. Automatic user localization consists of estimating the position of the user (latitude, longitude, and altitude) by using an electronic device, usually a mobile phone. Outdoor localization problem can be solved very accurately thanks to the inclusion of GPS sensors into the mobile devices.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Amazon reviews</title>
      <link>/projects/amazon-reviews/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/amazon-reviews/</guid>
      <description>OVERVIEW
Is it possible to predict the number of starts a user will give to a product based on the content of his review? Am I able to find different customer behaviours based on different products?
To be able to answer these questions will give me a better perspective of how customer client departments work on E-Commerce companies and do text mining to extract insights from it.

DATASET</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Avocado prices</title>
      <link>/projects/avocado-prices/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/avocado-prices/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tidytuesday: Marble Racing</title>
      <link>/blog/tidytuesday-marble-racing/tidytuesday-marble-racing/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jun 2020 17:34:14 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/tidytuesday-marble-racing/tidytuesday-marble-racing/</guid>
      <description>The following description comes from the TidyTuesday github.
 Jelle’s Marble Runs started as a quirky YouTube channel back in 2006 and has refined the art of marble racing to the point that many — including sponsor John Oliver from Last Week Tonight — consider marble racing a legitimate contender for the national sports spotlight. Given that Jelle’s Marble Runs just completed their popular Marbula One competition last month, I was curious to look at the race results to see if these races were anything more than chaos.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stack overflow 2018 survey analysis</title>
      <link>/blog/stackoverflow-survay-2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/stackoverflow-survay-2018/</guid>
      <description>OVERVIEW
The goal of this report is to analyse the stack overflow survey made in 2018, here is the link to the data. We will put the focus on developers working as data analysts and data scientists. The main questions to answer would be:
How much do they earn? We will only analyse the ones living in European countries like Germany, Spain or France. Which are the technologies they use?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Who eats the food we grow?</title>
      <link>/projects/world-food/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/world-food/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>